Finding Aid for the Albert Boime Papers LSC.1834
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Research materials, 1941-2008
  - Assorted Artists, 1972-2008
    - William Bouguereau, bulk 1975-1978, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, notes, annotated photocopies of letters, map of Bordeaux, France, paper "Decoration in Time, Decoration in Space: A Preliminary Discussion of Edgar Degas and Ballet Technique" by Janet Anderson, notes, 4x5 transparencies of Bouguereau works, and photo reprints. Correspondents include Miriam Gardner Dunnan. Some materials in French. File originally titled Boogie.
    - William Bouguereau, 1979, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Notes, correspondence, and photocopy. Correspondents include Miriam Gardner Dunnan and Stafford Calvin.
    - William Bouguereau (research files), 1978-1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Correspondence (postcards), map of Lyon, France, 4x5 transparencies of Bouguereau works, photo reprints of Bouguereau works, notes, bibliography, and photocopied article. Some materials in French.
    - William Bouguereau (class materials), undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Notes and materials for Art History 253 (2-quarter seminar on William Bouguereau and Modern Paris). Folder includes attendance list, syllabi, and lecture notes.
    - Weinberg's seminar, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Notes and bibliographies.
    - Tanenbaum catalog, bulk 1977-1978, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Correspondence (postcard), notes, photocopies, 6.5x10 transparency of J.J. Henner work "Le Levite d'Ephraim et sa femme morte," and pages from draft of Thomas Couture paper.
    - Kalan Brunink, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Notes, flyer for talk by Kalan Brunink, draft of paper "Kalan's Letter" (authorship unclear), correspondence with Kalan and others about her work, and copies of images of Kalan's portraits.
    - Eugene Carriere, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Bibliographic reference regarding Eugene Carriere.
    - George Catlin, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Draft of "George Catlin's Wilderness Utopia" by Boime with correspondence and contributor agreement for publication of paper.
    - Bergson and Cezanne, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
      Notes and photocopies about Paul Cezanne.
    - Paul Cezanne, 1998, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      E-mail correspondence, notes, draft of "Out of Time" by Fred Orton, and draft of "Cezanne's Real and Imagined Estate" by Boime.
    - Marc Chagall, ca. 1996, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      Exhibition brochures and images of stained glass windows.
    - Marc Chagall, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
      Notes, poem, and postcard.
    - Honore Daumier, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      Correspondence, draft of "Chapter VII: Fractures in the Juste Milieu," notes, and annotated photocopies of Daumier works.
    - Harvey Dinnerstein, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      Gallery catalog of Harvey Dinnerstein works and LINEA newsletters.
    - Simon Dinnerstein, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      Correspondence and draft of "Simon Dinnerstein's Family Romance" with edits.
    - Simon Dinnerstein, ca. 1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      Photocopies, correspondence, and images of Simon Dinnerstein works.
    - [Simon] Dinnerstein, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      Letter and photos of Simon Dinnerstein images.
    - Julius Kaplan, ca. 1994 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      Notes and correspondence. Potentially related to Simon Dinnerstein.
    - Don Demauro, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Draft of paper about Demauro "Don Demauro and the Struggle Against the Artist's Mystique." Folder also includes notes and a small notebook.
    - Don Demauro, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, photographic negatives, draft of paper "Don Demauro and the Struggle Against the Artist's Mystique," and Demauro curriculum vitae.
    - Thomas Eakins file, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Photocopy of volume on Thomas Eakins.
    - El Greco, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Notes and photocopy of article.
    - El Greco, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Correspondence with the Fundacion Amigos del Museo del Prado regarding a lecture by Boime entitled "El Greco. Obras Maestras."
    - El Greco miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - El Greco/Pollock, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, notes, and draft of "El Greco in New York: The Empowerment of Jackson Pollock" with some edits.
    - El Greco/Pollock, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Outline for paper "El Greco in New York: The Empowerment of Jackson Pollock." Folder also includes notes and receipts for airplane tickets.
    - EL Greco/Pollock, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Photocopies, correspondence, and notes.
    - El Greco/Pollock notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
      Annotated photocopies.
    - El Greco/SCW, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      Correspondence, notes, galley proof of Boime's article "El Greco in New York: The Empowerment of Jackson Pollock" in Spanish.
    - Unamuno/El Greco, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Paper "Les Demoiselles of 1898: Using Unamuno to Understand Picasso" by Michelle Tanenbaum, including a note to Boime.
    - Caspar David Friedrich, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      Photocopies, several copies of "Caspar David Friedrich: The Monk on the Seashore," UCLA Library newsletter, and correspondence. Some materials in German and Italian.
    - Friedrich talk, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
      Copy of "Caspar David Friedrich: The Monk on the Seashore." Text likely constitutes a lecture or talk delivered by Boime.
    - Paul Gauguin, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Notes, correspondence, Hammer museum exhibition brochure, and draft pages from paper regarding Gauguin's painting "Where do we come from? What are we? Where are we going?"
    - Paul Gauguin, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Notes and clipping.
    - Gauguin - colonialism, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Correspondence and notes.
    - Gauguin - revelation, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Jean-Leon Gerome, ca. 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Draft of "Gerome and the White Artist's Burden," photocopies, and correspondence.
    - Jean-Leon Gerome, ca. 1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Photos, notes, postcard, "St. Gerome and His World" lecture, and copies of images.
    - Jean-Leon Gerome, ca. 1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, notes, photocopies, and drafts of articles related Jean-Leon Gerome.
    - Jean-Leon Gerome, 1972, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Jean-Leon Gerome, ca. 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      Notes and art exhibition press release.
    - Gerome - Sleeping Gypsies, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Annotated draft of "Jean-Leon Gerome, Henri Rousseau's Sleeping Gypsy and the Academic Legacy," correspondence, and notes.
    - Anne-Louis Girodet, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Charles Gleyre, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
      Pages from draft "The Instruction of Charles Gleyre and the Evolution of Painting in the Nineteenth Century." See box 16 for addition research on Gleyre.
    - Charles Gleyre, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
      Photocopies. See box 16 for addition research on Gleyre.
    - Philip Guston, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      Correspondence with Intercambio de Arte y Cultura Internacional, Michoacán brochure, photocopy about Philip Guston, and copy of oral history interview with Frederick John de St. Vrain Schwankovsky.
    - Reuben Kadish and Philip Guston, 2005-2007 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      Copy of Kadish links and interview with Manuel Tolegian (oral history transcript). Folder also includes photocopies, correspondence, and prints of artwork.
    - Hildebrand, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
      Notes on Hildebrand.
    - Hogarth - 18th century, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Jean Auguste Dominique Ingres, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Prix de Rome - Ingres originals, ca. 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Drafts of "Prix de Rome: Images of Authority and Threshold of Official Success" speech and "Declassicizing the Academic and Accentuating the Affirmative." Folder also includes photos, correspondence, letter from Rose Weil and an incomplete Ingres draft.
    - Chavard, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Correspondence, photocopies, notes, and draft of paper "Ingress et Egress Chez Ingres" with edits. Some materials in French.
    - Kamran Khavarani, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, copies of images, notes with references to Rumi, and notes from interviews.
    - Khavarani, Kamran, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Notes and copy of poster advertising Kamran's work.
    - Abstract Romanticism: Kamran Khavarani, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Manuscript copy of "Abstract Romanticism: The Art and Passion of Kamran Khavarani."
    - Kamran Khavarani and the Birth of Abstract Romanticism, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Bound volume "Kamran Khavarani and the Birth of Abstract Romanticism" with illustrations and some writing.
    - Abstract Romanticism, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Correspondence regarding Boime's book "The Birth of Abstract Romanticism" and clippings.
    - Wassily Kandinsky, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Photos and images of works by Wassily Kandinsky.
    - Wassily Kandinsky, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Wassily Kandinsky, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Paul Klee, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      File contains a letter and orientalist photo and paper "Paul Klee and Christian Existentialism: Around the Fish."
    - Klee and primitive, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Klee and kids, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Franz Kline, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Draft of "Franz Kline and the Figurative Tradition" and notes.
    - Franz Kline, 1975, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Draft of "Franz Kline and the Figurative Tradition" with some edits, correspondence and notes
    - Franz Kline, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Notes, exhibition catalog, photograph of artwork, draft of lecture or proposal on Franz Kline's work, correspondence, photocopies, photographic negatives, and Franz Kline bibliography.
    - Franz Kline, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, notes, and 4 x 6 transparencies.
    - Fernand Leger, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ernest Lothar file, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Reference file about Lothar. Photos of Lothar's work taken by Helen Benson. Photocopies of news clippings about Lothar. Materials in file date from 1946-1952.
    - Franz Marc, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Notes on Franz Marc and Der Bleue Reiter.
    - Marisol, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Copy of article in American Art "The Postwar Redefinition of Self: Marisol's Yearbook Illustrations for the Class of '49" and drafts of same article. Folder also includes correspondence regarding photo permissions, clippings, photos, notes, 4x5 transparency, and photocopies.
    - Henri Matisse, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - McNeilly, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Notes and correspondence with Mike McNeilly regarding his mural. Folder also includes photography and 8x10 image of McNeilly mural.
    - Edvard Munch, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Notes on Munch.
    - Munch, ca. 1996 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Lecture outline, notes, and student paper regarding Edvard Munch. Materials potentially gathered for Princess Cruise lecture series.
    - Pablo Picasso, ca. 1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      Notes, correspondence, and exhibition brochure regarding Picasso works.
    - Pablo Picasso, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Catalog from Picasso exhibit at LACMA and lecture notes from Getty Lecture.
    - Pablo Picasso, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Notes, outline of Picasso lecture, and article "Picasso's Man with a Sheep: Beyond Good and Evil" by Albert Elsen.
    - Vincent Polo and Picasso, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Photocopies and images of Picasso artworks and inquiry documents regarding employment history of Vincent Polo.
    - Guernica, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
      Notes and materials from internet research.
    - Piero della Francesca, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Photocopies, notes, correspondence, and conference materials from National Gallery of Art on Piero Della Francesca symposium. Folder also includes drafts of "Piero and the Two Cultures" with edits.
    - Piero della Francesca II, bulk 1992, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Abstracts for Piero Della Francesca symposium with edits by Boime and draft of "Piero and the Two Cultures" with edits and galley proof of the same. Folder also includes correspondence and a clipping from Christian Science Monitor.
    - "Il Perugino" Institute, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Packet and business card about "Il Perugino" Institute.
    - Puvis de Chavannes, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Notes. See box 16 for additional research on Puvis de Chavannes.
    - Puvis - miscellaneous 19th century, ca. 1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Odilon Redon, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Notes on Odilon Redon (and Albert Ryder).
    - Repin, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      E-mail correspondence with Irina Tatarinova and faxed translations of text regarding Ilya Repin.
    - Auguste Rodin, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Rodin paper, 1994, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Student paper "Sculpture Seen Through Rodin" by Ashkan Lashkari for Art History 199 with Boime in Spring 1996 and paper "Mengs' Parnassus & David's Victors Returning to Brutus the Bodies of his Sons: Recapturing and Redefining Antiquity" by same student for Art History 110A.
    - Victor Hugo, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Notes on Rodin's monument to Victor Hugo.
    - Runge, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Albert Pinkham Ryder - Brooklyn, 1972, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      Correspondence, draft of paper by Eric Rosenberg, and draft of "Ryder on a Gilded Horse" with edits.
    - Raphael Soyer, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      Notes and obituaries about Raphael Soyer. See box 59 for additional research on Raphael Soyer.
    - Sargent drafts, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Miscellaneous pages from drafts on John Singer Sargent with edits (out of order).
    - Sargent notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
      Notes and New York Times World of New York fliers.
    - Sargent symposium, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      Notes and business cards. Bulk of folder contains correspondence with H. Barbara Weinberg and a draft of her lecture for a symposium on John Singer Sargent.
    - John Singer Sargent, 1982, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      John Singer Sargent articles, 4x5 transparencies, miscellaneous pages from draft on Sargent, notes, and correspondence. Folder also includes a Guide to Research at the Historic New Orleans Collection and photocopies of materials from Historic New Orleans Collection (specifically Trist Wood Papers Inventory, copies of photos, and paperwork from Survey of New Orleans cemeteries).
    - Sargent correspondence (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Correspondence regarding Sargent images, consultations, and research for Boime's co-authorship of a Sargent catalog. Other materials include a draft of a Sargent paper with edits, notes, annotated photocopies, and paper "Sargent and Venice" by Linda Ayers. Some materials in French.
    - Sargent correspondence (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Schoneberg, ca. 2002 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Copies of works by S.C. Schoneberg.
    - Jane Wooster Scott and Walter Keane, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, descriptive articles about Jane Wooster Scott and Walter Keane, and photocopies of book about Walter Keane. Other materials include gallery brochures and publications, some photos of artwork, and notes.
    - Mike Tanzer (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Correspondence, drafts of "Michael Tanzer: An Artist Searching for His Routes" with edits, notes, photocopied articles and clippings, and slides.
    - Mike Tanzer (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Tattoo, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Paper (likely by Michael Tanzer) "Outermost Boundaries: Challenging Assumptions about Art," regarding tattoo art.
    - Tattoo Writings, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Draft of paper/article on tattoos.
    - Velasquez, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Bibliographic reference regarding Velasquez. Possibly referring to Diego Velazquez.
    - Vuillard, ca. 1998 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Copy of Thesis "Symbiosis: Edward Vuillard and the Natansons in Fin de Siècle Paris" by Heloise Bertman Levit.
    - Warshaw, 1959-1981 (bulk 1960s) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Photocopies of clippings about Howard Warshaw and his works.
    - Offbeat artists, 1989, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Gallery brochures, correspondence, various exhibition announcements, and articles.
  - Research Notes and Notebooks, bulk 1963-1978, 2000-2003
    Research notes and notebooks that are not easily attributable to a specific research topic. A large volume of the material includes notebooks filled with notes, likely from the beginning of Boime's academic career. There are also some notebooks from Boime's research in a French archive and original documents collected by Jean-Jacques Pick (a member of the Salon d'Automne). This subseries is filed topically by type of material.
    - Articles, undated (Box 137, Folder 6)
      Photocopies. Some materials in French.
    - Original documents (1 of 2), 1916-1936 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, clippings, and legal documents collected by Jean-Jacques Pick (member of Salon d'Automne). Some materials in French and Greek. The time at which Boime collected these materials is unclear, but the items date from 1916-1936.
    - Original documents (2 of 2), 1916-1936 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Lecture note cards, undated (Box 148, Folder 1)
      Numbered note cards likely from a lecture delivered by Boime at the 10th anniversary of the Patricia McCarron McGinn series.
    - Note cards, undated (Box 148, Folder 2)
      Note card catalog of artworks with identifying collection information.
    - Research note cards, undated (Box 149, Folder 1)
      Topics include Feuerbach, Gerome, and Manet.
    - Notes and correspondence, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Correspondence regarding a lecture by Boime and notes. Some materials in German.
    - Notes and correspondence, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Miscellaneous notes and correspondence with faculty. Some materials in French.
    - Notes and correspondence, 1978, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Paper "British Painting 1750-1850/The Rebels" by Lilian Staple, notes on American religious painting, and photocopies of correspondence to Esther Williams in the early 20th century.
    - Notes, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      Notes (topics include Thomas Nast) and memo regarding department philosophy and discussions from Don Preziosi.
    - Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
      Notes and scribbles on Art 563 syllabus.
    - Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
      Notes and sheet of images.
    - Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
      Miscellaneous pages from a draft and notes.
    - Notes, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Notes, ca. 1963 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      Notes (topics include Hofstra, Charles Henry, Seurat, and Couture), correspondence, negatives, clippings, photocopies, and miscellaneous pages from draft "I don't want to set the world on fire, I just want to start a flame in your heart" with edits.
    - Notes, 1973, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      Correspondence and notes (topics include Simon Dinnerstein).
    - Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
      Notes from correspondence with Francois Gerard (topics include Girodet).
    - Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Notes, ca. 1978 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      Notes, correspondence, paper submissions, and syllabus for Art History 110B (taught by David Kunzle).
    - Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      Notes (topics include monuments, colonialism, modern art), photocopies, and correspondence regarding Boime's library loans. Other materials include drafts of minutes and agendas from Art History department meetings.
    - Miscellaneous biographies, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Research materials, 1995, 1997, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, notes, and bibliographies (topics include Mexico and Masonic influence, Seurat, Gauguin, Van Gogh, and the French-Jewish press).
    - Miscellaneous research, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Paper "Action Potential Alternans and Irregular Dynamics in Quinidine-Intoxicated Ventricular Muscle Cells," notes, and correspondence.
    - Miscellaneous research, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Notes and correspondence from Wendy Slatkin.
    - Research notes (1 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Research notes (2 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Notes 1, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Notebooks with notes on miscellaneous topics, such as early modern art, early Christian art, Courbet, and realism. Notebooks are likely from Boime's graduate studies.
    - Notes 2, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Notebooks with notes on topics like educational policy. Notebooks are likely from Boime's graduate studies.
    - Notes 3, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Notebooks with notes on topics like economics, social issues, and race relations. Notebooks are likely from Boime's graduate studies.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Research notebooks: topics include Vernet, Journal des Artistes, Delaroche, Ottin, Sculpture, Deperthes, Gleyre, Salon Refuses and Jury, and Henner. Some materials in French.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Research notebooks: topics include Manette, sketches, David, bibliographie, Salon de Refuses, and Monet.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Research notebooks: topics include Stranahan, Revue des deux mondes, and Dimier.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Research notebooks: topics include the Academy.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Research notebooks: topics include Ottin, Salon de Refuses, and revue des deux mondes.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Research notebooks: topics include Couture, encyclopedie, and juste milieu.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Research notebooks: topics include Georg Sauter and Manuel Arsenne.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Research notebooks: topics include Prudhomme. Some materials in French and German.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Research notebooks: topics include Beaux-Arts. Some materials in French and German.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Research notebooks: topics/authors include Ingres, Pisanello, Magic-Copy, and John Singer Sargent.
    - Research notebooks, ca. 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Research notebooks: topics include the English Academy, Impressionism, and 1851 Catalogue. Some materials in German.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Some materials in French.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Some materials in German and Italian.
    - Research notebooks, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Some materials in Spanish.
    - Archives research notebooks, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Research notebooks on materials in unidentified archive. Materials in French.
    - Archives research notebooks, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Archives research notebooks, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Bibliography, undated (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Unlabeled notes, undated (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Modern Art Series, 1971-1997, 2000-2006